如果我是一只动物
如果我是天鹅
艾玛：如果我是一只动物
If I were an animal,
我要做一只天鹅
I'd like to be a swan.
蒂姆：那你就会生活在大河上了
And you'd live on a large river.
艾玛：蒂姆 它们在跳舞吗
Tim, are they dancing?
蒂姆：我觉得它们一定很相爱
I think that's how they say they love each other.
如果它们在筑巢的话 也就是说
Ah, if they're building a nest that means...
艾玛：它们马上要生宝宝啦
They're gonna have babies!
啊哦 天鹅爸爸好像生气了
Uh oh...Daddy Swan looks mad.
蒂姆：它肯定是在保护什么
He must be trying to protect something…
艾玛：是天鹅妈妈的蛋
Mama Swan's eggs!
蒂姆 为什么它要把蛋翻过来
Tim, why is she turning them over?
蒂姆：为了给它们保暖
To keep them warm.
啊 快看
Awwww  Look!
艾玛：太可爱了
They're so cute!
我们叫它毛毛吧
She can be called Fluff…
那只就叫路路
the other one can be called Floof…
灰色那只叫丽丽
and this grey one can be called Fliff!
蒂姆：嘿毛毛 别啄丽丽的脚
Hey Fluff, don't peck on Fliff's foot!
巢里大家都有位置
There's room for everyone in the nest!
艾玛：小宝宝们去哪了
Where are the babies?
啊 在这了
Oh! There they are
水肯定很冷
The water must be so cold!
不过毛毛很聪明
Fluff's super smart though.
如果我是天鹅宝宝
If I were a baby swan,
我也会想待在暖和又舒适的地方
I'd wanna stay somewhere cozy and warm too.
嘿 它在做什么
Hey, what's she doing??
快看 蒂姆 丽丽要自己飞了
Look, Tim! Fliff's going off by himself!
蒂姆：小心点 丽丽
Careful, Fliff!
艾玛：啊哦 那只大鸟想要做什么
Uh oh, what does that big birdie want?
蒂姆：我记得这种鸟叫鸬鹚
I think it's called the Cormorant!
艾玛：走吧 丽丽 毛毛 路路
Off you go, Fliff, Fluff and Floof!
天鹅爸爸好像生大鸟的气了
Daddy Swan looks angry at the big bird.
艾玛：丽丽加油 你可以的 上上上
Come on Fliff, you can do it! Go go go...
好了 天鹅爸爸
Alright, Daddy Swan,
现在示威够了吧
that's enough showing off for now.
蒂姆&艾玛：啊
Awwwww
蒂姆：飞行课 如何起飞
Flying lesson: how to take off!
我说的是起飞 不是装傻
I said "take off", not be silly...!
艾玛：我喜欢它站在水上的样子
I like the way he pushes up on his feet!
哦不 下次好运啦 丽丽
Oh no! Better luck next time Fliff…
蒂姆：它已经尽力了
He's trying his best…!
艾玛：别放弃 丽丽 马上就成功了
Don't give up Fliff, you're almost there!
就是这样 看看别人
That's it, watch the others!
蒂姆：哇
Wow!
毛毛和路路起飞啦
Fluff and Floof are taking off!!
艾玛：那丽丽呢
But what about Fliff?
蒂姆：别担心 它马上就成功了
Don't worry, he'll be next…
看 艾玛 天鹅爸爸在帮它
Look Emma, his dad is helping him!
艾玛：加油丽丽
C'mon, Fliff !
你能行的
You can do it…
蒂姆：哦耶
Ah yeah!
艾玛：加油丽丽
Go Fliff!
艾玛&蒂姆：哇
Wow!
蒂姆：爸爸妈妈很为你骄傲
Mom and Dad are very proud of you.
干得好 丽丽 你已经成年啦
Well done, Fliff. You're all grown-up.
艾玛：再见 丽丽
Bye bye Fliff…